Gabrielle Giffords Papers, 1995-2012 (bulk 2007-2012)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup III: January 8, 2011 Tucson, Arizona shooting, 2011-2012
  - Series 4: Memorabilia, 2010-2012
    - Book: Honorary Save-A-Life Saturday, 2011 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Book: Office guestbook sign-in, 2011 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Book: Photos and poetry, Patagonia schools, 2011 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Book: Together We Thrive, 2011 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Book: Sam Farr Town Hall well wishes scrapbook, undated (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Bracelets: In Support of Giffords, undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Calendar: Military Jets from The Institute for Rehabilitation and Research, 2011 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Arizona Planned Parenthood well wishes (1 of 2), undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Arizona Planned Parenthood well wishes (2 of 2), undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Congressional well wishes, February 9, 2011 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Congressional well wishes, undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Food Drive well wishes, Sierra Vista, Arizona, February 9, 2011 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Manfred Woerner trip attendees well wishes, undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Operation Enduring Freedom 10-11 Task Force Tigershark well wishes, January, 2011 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Poem, I Shall Conquer, March 19, 2011 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Toronto Vigil for Tucson Victims well wishes, January 22, 2011 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Dedication: Tucson Symphony Orchestra, 2011 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Flag: 354th Expeditionary Fighter Squadron recognition, Davis-Monthan Air Force Base, Arizona, January 13, 2010 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Flag: Descendants of Mr. Emanuel Garcia Levy, State of Arizona, January 26, 2012 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Flag: Operation New Dawn with Operation Iraqi Freedom medal, January 29, 2011-February 7, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Flag: SOC Matt Bissonnette, Special Operations Mission, January 9, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Memorial: Tucson Shooting Victims of January 8, 2011, Golder Ranch & Northwest Fire District, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Proclamation: New York State Assembly, February 10, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Proclamations and Resolutions, 2011-2012 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Programs: Services and Celebrations, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Resolution: City of Bedford Heights, February 17, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Resolution: H. Res. 32, January 12, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Sheet Music: Calling Gabrielle, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Shoe: Reverends Mary and Milton Cole-Duvall well wishes, March 4, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Well-wishing collection box, undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Subgroup IV: Electronic records